RG 062:020, Town of Burlington
Connecticut State Library
Town of Burlington records
1799-1919
Connecticut State Library
Burlington (Conn.)
10.75 cubic feet
Selectmen, election, justice of the peace, land, financial, school and tax records for the town of Burlington.
RG062_020
T000615
Historical Note
The town of Burlington was incorporated in May 1806 and was taken from Bristol.
Scope and Content
Selectmen, election, justice of the peace, land, financial, school and tax records for the town of Burlington.
Index Terms
Alternate Creator:
Connecticut. Justice of the Peace (Burlington)
Subjects:
Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Burlington -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Burlington -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Burlington -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Burlington -- Registers; Voting registers -- Connecticut -- Burlington; School enrollment -- Connecticut -- Burlington -- Statistics; Justices of the peace -- Connecticut -- Burlington
Places:
Burlington (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1799-1919
  - Selectmen's incoming correspondence, lists of deeds, and contracts for taking the poor, 1888-1903 (Box Box 1)
  - Registers of electors, 1837-1870 (Box Box 1)
  - Elector's certificates, circa 1824-1876 (Box Box 1)
  - Appointments of Justices of the Peace and overseers, 1832-1850 (Box Box 1)
  - Town officers' bonds, 1878-1900 (Box Box 2)
  - Deeds, 1878-1898 (Box Box 2)
  - Road contracts, 1882-1896 (Box Box 2)
  - Reports of town votes, 1824-1869 (Box Box 2)
  - Town accounts, 1878-1900 (Box Box 3)
  - School accounts, 1890-1900 (Box Box 3)
  - School Fund receipt and account book, 1799-1809 (Box Box 3)
  - School registers, 1915-1926 (Box Boxes 4-5)
  - Attachments, 1802-1862 (Box Boxes 6-7)
  - Justice files, 1828-1846 (Box Box 7)
  - Tax abstracts
    Boxes 9, 10, and 17 are on oversize shelving.
    - 1806, 1807, 1808, 1809, 1810, 1811, 1812, 1813, 1814, 1815, 1816, 1817, 1818, 1819, 1820, 1821, 1822, 1823, 1824, 1825, 1826, 1827, 1828, 1829, 1830 (Box Box 8)
    - 1831, 1832, 1833, 1834, 1835, 1836, 1837, 1838, 1839, 1840, 1841, 1842, 1843, 1844, 1845, 1846, 1847, 1848, 1849 (Box Box 9)
    - 1850, 1851, 1852, 1853, 1854, 1855, 1856, 1857, 1858, 1859 (Box Box 10)
    - 1860, 1861, 1862, 1863, 1864, 1865, 1866, 1867, 1868, 1869 (Box Box 11)
    - 1870, 1871, 1872, 1873, 1874, 1875, 1876, 1877, 1878, 1879 (Box Box 12)
    - 1880, 1881, 1882, 1883, 1884, 1885, 1886, 1887 (Box Box 13)
    - 1888, 1889, 1890, 1891, 1892, 1893, 1894 (Box Box 14)
    - 1895, 1896, 1897, 1898, 1899, 1900, 1901 (Box Box 15)
    - 1902, 1903, 1904, 1905, 1906, 1907, 1908, 1909, 1910 (Box Box 16)
    - 1911, 1912, 1913, 1914, 1915, 1916, 1917, 1918, 1919 (Box Box 17)